Did you know that every year in India,
millions of people either go bankrupt due to medical emergencies
or are unable to afford treatment due to lack of money? This is
a major problem. With rising hospital
expenses, this problem has become even
bigger, the complete solution for which
is a health insurance policy. Friends,
keeping this in mind, we try our best to bring you videos of all the
latest advanced health insurance
products through our channel.
Today's video is
our next step in this direction. We will talk about
ICICI Lombard's flagship
product, ICICI Health Advantage.
In the video, I will
not only tell you the features and benefits of the product,
but as a tip, I will also tell you about the
quality of the product,
which we decide on the product's
features, benefits, cleanliness, etc.,
along with many factors. But to
know all this, it is important for you to
stay with me till the very end of the video.
And yes, if you haven't subscribed to our channel yet, then do so
quickly.  Do
n't forget to subscribe and press the bell icon so that
you keep getting notifications of all our upcoming videos from time to
time. So let's start.
This is by Dharamveer Singh and you are watching
Aapke Fail Ki Baat
Bangladesh Bowling Before.
ICICI Health Advantage is a very
advanced health insurance product in which
you get worldwide coverage along with
many optional benefits, with the
help of which you can customize your product
according to your retirement.
For example, if you
want maternity cover in the policy, you want newborn baby cover
and you also want to cover the baby's vaccination, then for this
you can get a
rider by paying a little additional premium in the policy.
To avail the maternity benefit, it is necessary that you pay 3 years'
premium lump sum to the company. After that, you get
10% of your amount or maximum up
to Rs 10 lakh as maternity cover. The
company provides you double the amount of your maternity cover as newborn baby cover and baby
You can claim up to ₹10,000 for vaccination.
Most importantly,
your maternity cover gets activated in the policy after a waiting period of only 9 months.
Similarly,
major critical expenses
exhaust 100% of our policy's total amount,
after which we are left with no cover available for normal horseplay.
Keeping this in mind, the policy has been
given Critical Illness Raigarh, with the
help of which you
can avail additional critical illness cover of up to ₹50 lakh.
If you want to cover accidental death or
total permanent disability or
total partial disability due to an accident, then for this
you can
add a personal accident rider of up to ₹50 lakh to the policy.
With the help of Protector Rider, the
risk cover of your policy
increases every year according to inflation
and with the help of Claim Protector Rider,
you can cover all non-items.  You can also cover these in your policy.
Friends, ICICI
Health Advantage is a health insurance policy with a
quality score of 75,
which we have determined to be very good
based on multiple factors. The company's
claim settlement ratio is 86%, and
only seven out of every 10,000 customers file a claim-
related complaint.
100% of claims are settled in just 30 days.
To ensure maximum risk coverage, the policy
offers a restoration benefit, which is
activated after a single claim
and is applicable for any individual, disease, or condition throughout the year. The
company's wellness
program and other value-added services
contribute significantly to this product's quality rating. Through the wellness program, the
company provides free health
checkups every year. If you take
good care of your fitness, the
company earns reward points, based on which
you can earn a significant discount on your renewal premium.  You
can gain if
you avail value-added services like
unlimited free online doctor consultation,
medicine and diagnostic services, and
free-of-cost healthcare services. The policy has
no down payment and a guaranteed no-live bonus. You
get no liability in case of a claim.
After just two years, the policy covers all pre-
existing and specified diseases. The
eligibility criteria and basic features of the policy are as follows:
Any individual between the age of 18 and 65 years can purchase this policy
as an individual policy
or can cover his/her entire family
under a family floater policy.
This policy covers two adults and three
children. You can also include
your parents, brother-in-
law, and sister-in-law. This
advanced product covers all treatments like in-patient, house-care,
domicile, home care,
Ayurvedic, Yoga, Unani,
Siddha, and homeopathic. The
policy covers
90  Along with free hospitalization for 10 days and
post-hospitalization for 180 days,
you also get facilities like organ donor cover, expenses, surface
ambulance, and domestic air ambulance.
Domestic
air ambulance expenses are
not included in your basic sum assured.
Apart from this, many
advanced treatments are covered in the policy with a gap,
such as
you get ₹10,000 for animal bite vaccination,
₹25,000 for home care treatment,
and ₹10 lakh for battery surgery.
If you are hospitalized for more than 10 days, the company pays you
a lump sum amount of ₹20,000 as a benefit.
So, this is a one-of-a-kind finance health
insurance product, which is designed keeping
in mind your illness as well as your wellness.
And I hope you
liked this policy very much. Still,
if you have any related issues,  If you have any and you want
me to respond to you as quickly as possible,
then you can comment by pressing the thanks button
and for any further consultation,
your financial planning or
any issue related to your claim, you can
contact me personally on my
mobile number
9810411. So friends, that's all for today. I will meet
you in the next video
with some other benefit for you. Take
care.